[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This will fade a tattoo over time.", "correct_answer": "Sunlight", "incorrect_answers": ["Washing substances", "Water", "The change of skin structure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Apart from The Wizard of Oz, little people, or midgets, were used in what other Top Ten picture, to help achieve a visual effect?", "correct_answer": "Casablanca", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Big Man", "Gone With the Wind", "Little Women"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What title did Sarah Ferguson assume upon marrying Queen Elizabeth IIs second son, Prince Andrew?", "correct_answer": "Duchess of York", "incorrect_answers": ["Duchess of Edinburgh", "Princess Royal", "Princess of York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Denzel Washington was banned from watching movies as a child.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Special Agent Johnny Utah, played by Keanu Reeves in Point Break, is a former quarterback for what university?", "correct_answer": "Ohio State", "incorrect_answers": ["Michigan State", "Notre Dame", "Michigan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the name of the American printmaking firm that produced prints by hand-colored lithography: ........... and Ives.", "correct_answer": "Currier", "incorrect_answers": ["Crasnston", "Cuttler", "Commings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Edgar Allan Poe is known to be the father of detective stories. What was he often characterized as?", "correct_answer": "Alcoholic", "incorrect_answers": ["Womanizer", "Homosexual", "Melancholic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which natural disaster claimed the most lives during the second millennium?", "correct_answer": "influenza", "incorrect_answers": ["earthquakes", "tsunami", "plague"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the ROM part of a CD-ROM stand for?", "correct_answer": "Read Only Memory", "incorrect_answers": ["Erase Only Memory", "Nothing", "Romial Memory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the currency of the Netherlands, before the adoption of the euro?", "correct_answer": "Gulden", "incorrect_answers": ["Dinar", "Krona", "Florin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1985 movie St. Elmos Fire?", "correct_answer": "Joel Schumacher", "incorrect_answers": ["John Hughes", "Joe Johnston", "Joel Zwick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The plot of the movie The Da Vinci Code revolves around The Priory of Sion, a European secret society founded in 1099. Which of these people was not  mentioned as a member of that organization?", "correct_answer": "Bezu Fache", "incorrect_answers": ["Jacques Sauni\u00e8re", "Sir isaac Newton", "Leonardo Da Vinci"]}]